So now we are going to create our first practical project and we are going to get the Uuid of classic
cards.
So the things we need to create this project is Arduino Uno and we need RC five five to module that
is over here.
You can see it.
And then we also need four pin.
So this is the Led which has four pins.
So you need this led as well.
And then we need breadboard jumper wire for the next project.
We also need Buzzer.
So I have also included buzzer into it.
And then we need Mifare classic cards.
So these are the hardware requirements for this project, right?
So in this project we are going to get the Uuid of Mifare classic cards and then we are going to create
a simple, valid Uid program in which we are going to get the valid cards and invalid cards.
Right?
So this is the next project we are going to see and we are going to use the same hardware in the coming
up project as well.
So for now these are the requirements.
So you if you want to follow up, make sure you have all these hardwares with you.
Right?
So we are going to create the hardware in the next video.